<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>



<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Treasure</title>
    <description>Treasure is a utility app offering a digital collection service that helps content creators digitalize, manage, and share highlight moments with their fans.</description>
    <link>https://www.google.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.google.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 19:26:05 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 19:26:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Siteleaf</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Join us on GitHub Discussions</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://community.siteleaf.com&quot;&gt;Siteleaf Community&lt;/a&gt; now has a new home on GitHub Discussions where you can get help, vote on new features, and share what you’re working on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To get started we created topics for:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;❓ &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/siteleaf/community/discussions/categories/community-support&quot;&gt;Community Support&lt;/a&gt;: Ask the community for help.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;💡 &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/siteleaf/community/discussions/categories/feature-requests&quot;&gt;Feature Requests&lt;/a&gt;: Vote and share ideas for new features.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;🙌 &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/siteleaf/community/discussions/categories/show-tell&quot;&gt;Show &amp;amp; Tell&lt;/a&gt;: Show off something you’ve made.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;💬 &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/siteleaf/community/discussions/categories/general-discussion&quot;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt;: Everything else.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GitHub Discussions will replace our existing Slack community, and we look forward to building a more open, accessible, and searchable archive for questions that pop up often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also hope to offer a greater level of transparency by opening up our roadmap and allowing the community to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/siteleaf/community/discussions/categories/feature-requests&quot;&gt;vote on new features&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;most-helpful&quot;&gt;Most helpful&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll be rewarding the most helpful community members with exclusive perks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/github-discussions-most-helpful.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of GitHub Discussions showing most helpful community members&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GitHub will automatically recognize community members who contribute the most comments marked as answers within the past 30 days in the Community Support section. If you see your name in the leaderboard, we’ll be in touch to give you some exclusive perks as a thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us at: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://community.siteleaf.com&quot;&gt;https://community.siteleaf.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; →&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 14:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.google.com/blog/join-us-on-github-discussions/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.google.com/blog/join-us-on-github-discussions/</guid>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>announcement</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing Siteleaf VIP: our affiliate program</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we are officially launching our much requested affiliate program: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vip.siteleaf.com/signup&quot;&gt;Siteleaf VIP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We know a lot of our customers use Siteleaf with clients (and enjoy referring friends and colleagues), so we’re excited to say thanks and give back!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For every new user who signs up with your unique VIP link, you’ll earn a 30% commission for any paid sites they create. Depending on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/plans&quot;&gt;plan&lt;/a&gt; chosen, you could earn over $1,000/year for a single referral — which recurs for as long as the site is active. For freelancers, this is a nice way to add a little recurring revenue to your income.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-it-works&quot;&gt;How it works&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vip.siteleaf.com/signup&quot;&gt;Sign up&lt;/a&gt; to create a unique referral link, and share this with your clients and colleagues. Feel free to add this link to your website footer and share it on social media. It looks something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;https://www.siteleaf.com/?via=yourname
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tip&quot;&gt;You can link to any page on siteleaf.com by adding &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;?via=yourname&lt;/code&gt; to the end of the URL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All you need to get started is a PayPal account, and you can keep track of your leads and conversions using the VIP dashboard at: &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vip.siteleaf.com&quot;&gt;https://vip.siteleaf.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; →&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for using Siteleaf and continuing to spread the word!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 10:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.google.com/blog/vip-affiliate-program/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.google.com/blog/vip-affiliate-program/</guid>
        
        <category>announcement</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading to Jekyll 4</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Jekyll 4.0 is out in the world, and brings upon many improvements over 3.x.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notably, your site should build &lt;em&gt;much&lt;/em&gt; faster now thanks to super-powered caching and content transformations. You can see a &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/news/2019/08/20/jekyll-4-0-0-released/&quot;&gt;full list of changes here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While GitHub Pages is still pinned to &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/versions/&quot;&gt;Jekyll 3.8.x&lt;/a&gt;, it’s possible to start using Jekyll 4 today with a little help from Siteleaf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out our upgrade guide to get started: &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://learn.siteleaf.com/themes/upgrading-from-jekyll-3-to-4/&quot;&gt;Upgrading from Jekyll 3.x to 4.x&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; →&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s to speedy rendering! 🍃&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 10:41:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.google.com/blog/upgrading-to-jekyll-4/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.google.com/blog/upgrading-to-jekyll-4/</guid>
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>github</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New sites in our gallery</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re biased, but we think the best sites use Siteleaf. Some of our favorites include &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.antfood.com/&quot;&gt;Antfood&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://capitolciderhouse.com/&quot;&gt;Capitol Cider House&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://thecreativeindependent.com//&quot;&gt;The Creative Independent&lt;/a&gt;. This week we added five new sites to our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/gallery/&quot;&gt;gallery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;super-brewing-co&quot;&gt;Super Brewing Co.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/super-brewing.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Super Brewing Co.'s website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://superbrewing.co/&quot;&gt;Super Brewing Co.&lt;/a&gt; is an independent nano-brewery based in Oregon, who specialize making super beer. Their site is full of lovely design details &amp;amp; moments of joy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;listen-up-biz&quot;&gt;Listen Up Biz&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/listen-up-f43ab5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Listen Up's website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.listen-up.biz/&quot;&gt;Listen Up Biz&lt;/a&gt; provides a bespoke 360 promotional service offering radio, club, streaming promotion and press campaigns globally. We love the hype video on their home page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bloomvale&quot;&gt;Bloomvale&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/bloomvale-ef3aec.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Bloomvale's website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bloomvale.com/&quot;&gt;Bloomvale&lt;/a&gt; work with CEOs and their senior management teams to drive growth and help technology and media companies. Their clean and simple website is a typographic delight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;quinn-cantwell&quot;&gt;Quinn Cantwell&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/quinn-cantwell.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Quinn's website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://quinncantwell.com/&quot;&gt;Quinn Cantwell&lt;/a&gt; is a San Francisco-based video director who has worked with the likes of Everlane, SoulCycle, and Opening Ceremony. The straightforward design allows her work to shine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dropmark&quot;&gt;Dropmark&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Dropmark.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Dropmark's website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back with a fresh new design, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dropmark.com/&quot;&gt;Dropmark&lt;/a&gt; is a tool for teams and individuals to gather inspiration, share, and collaborate privately. The new ‘human-focussed’ look is an exciting step. &lt;em&gt;Full disclosure, Siteleaf and Dropmark are both made by &lt;a href=&quot;https://oak.is/&quot;&gt;Oak Studios&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;See all the other sites #builtwithsiteleaf on our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/gallery/&quot;&gt;gallery&lt;/a&gt;. 
Want to see your website in our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/gallery/&quot;&gt;gallery&lt;/a&gt;? Get in touch on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/siteleaf&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:support@siteleaf.com&quot;&gt;email us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 12:18:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.google.com/blog/new-sites-in-our-gallery/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.google.com/blog/new-sites-in-our-gallery/</guid>
        
        <category>inspiration</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to check your site for broken links</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Clicking on links that are broken is a bad experience for users, and it can even affect your &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/blog/seo-with-jekyll-siteleaf/&quot;&gt;SEO&lt;/a&gt;. Thankfully, it’s really easy to automate the process of checking the links on your site using &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;html-proofer&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can install &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;html-proofer&lt;/code&gt; however you like, for the sake of argument we’ll use &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;bundle&lt;/code&gt; by adding the following to your &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gemfile&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-sh highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;gem &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'rake'&lt;/span&gt;
gem &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'html-proofer'&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then run &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;bundle install&lt;/code&gt;. Then you can get &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;html-proofer&lt;/code&gt; to check for any broken links using the following commands:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-sh highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;bundle &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;exec &lt;/span&gt;jekyll build
bundle &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;exec &lt;/span&gt;htmlproofer ./_site&lt;span class=&quot;sb&quot;&gt;`&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then you’ll receive a breakdown of every external and internal link which is broken. Go forth and fix things! Hat’s off to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.supertechcrew.com/jekyll-check-for-broken-links/&quot;&gt;Super Tech Crew&lt;/a&gt; for this tip. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 11:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.google.com/blog/how-to-check-your-site-for-broken-links/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.google.com/blog/how-to-check-your-site-for-broken-links/</guid>
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tip</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Antfood</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;antfood-is-a-creative-audio-studio-with-offices-in-brooklyn-amsterdam-and-são-paulo&quot;&gt;Antfood is a creative audio studio with offices in Brooklyn, Amsterdam, and São Paulo.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are all about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.antfood.com/&quot;&gt;Antfood’s website&lt;/a&gt;, which is built with Siteleaf. In particular, their loading animations inject a touch of humor to the site, which transforms a potentially boring wait into a moment of joy. This playful style translates directly into their work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s one of the only portfolios where exploring and finding hidden gems feels like an exciting quest and a considered part of the user journey, rather than an afterthought. This thoughtfulness is perhaps unsurprising as the site was designed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.xxix.co/&quot;&gt;XXIX&lt;/a&gt;, who make amazing treats for the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;we-chatted-with-wilson-brown-ecd-and-partner-at-antfood-about-curiosity-collaboration-and-the-year-ahead&quot;&gt;We chatted with Wilson Brown, ECD and Partner at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.antfood.com/&quot;&gt;Antfood&lt;/a&gt;, about curiosity, collaboration, and the year ahead.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;can-you-tell-me-about-antfood-and-how-you-got-to-where-you-are-now&quot;&gt;Can you tell me about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.antfood.com/&quot;&gt;Antfood&lt;/a&gt;, and how you got to where you are now?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.antfood.com/&quot;&gt;Antfood&lt;/a&gt; in 2007 and have grown slowly from there. I felt we had drive and some basic talent, but truthfully we were kids with little experience, no connections and zero capital. We got to where we are now by focusing on making great work and seeking out great collaborators, colleagues and projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel very grateful for the successes that we’ve had, and I’m proud of the reputation that we’ve built, but it was achieved very slowly, by taking little steps to improve our craft, team, physical studio, instruments, equipment, and over the years our portfolio. Even now, we’re still trying to do the same thing every day, to take on new challenges, hone our craft and do things that no one has done before — or at least we haven’t tried yet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/273782257?color=ffffff&amp;amp;title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;youve-collaborated-with-some-fantastic-companies-are-there-any-pieces-of-work-that-you-continue-to-look-back-on-and-think-damn-thats-great&quot;&gt;You’ve collaborated with some fantastic companies, are there any pieces of work that you continue to look back on and think ‘damn, that’s great’?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for the kind words. We take pride in building relationships and actively try to find like-minded creative collaborators, who we can help elevate their craft, and they can help elevate ours. &lt;a href=&quot;http://buck.tv/#/&quot;&gt;Buck Design&lt;/a&gt; has been a great collaborator over the years, and we’ve worked together on the number of pieces together since 2009, that have been seminal for Antfood regarding process and creative, and I hope the same is true for Buck too!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I rarely look back at old work on a day-to-day basis, but often when we’re putting together talks for conferences or festivals, revamping our website or social presence, or just reflecting on our mission and values past and present, I love seeing the work we’ve done over the years. Sometimes these are big portfolio pieces, and sometimes they are forgotten or ignored projects, and I love seeing tiny strokes of genius, humor and artistry within the more generic projects, that you don’t necessarily appreciate at the time when you’re in the thick of production, approvals, and delivery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/38386297?color=ffffff&amp;amp;title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pedro and I are putting together a talk for a conference in Amsterdam next week, and I came across a couple of pieces that I had pushed to the back of my mind, but still love &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.antfood.com/load/#freebord-8-bit&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Freebord&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (2009), &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.antfood.com/load/#come-together&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sundance&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (2010), &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.antfood.com/load/#2017-show-opening-titles&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;AICP&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (2017). Also, a perennial favorite, that was played out back in 2012, but I still I love going back to is our deconstructed, and dingy Kafka-esque piece with Buck, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.antfood.com/load/#good-books-metamorphosis&quot;&gt;Metamorphosis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; for Good Books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-does-your-creative-process-look-like&quot;&gt;What does your creative process look like?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In composition, I try to vary my process, to ensure that I’m coming up with new and different ideas sounds, harmonies and textures. That can influence what kind of instruments or structural form I begin with, and what I deem the central elements of the composition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, sometimes I’ll start with a beat or a harmonic framework and build everything up around that, other times I’ll start with the opinion, the voice or even a more abstract point of view and use what musical and arrangement tools I need to convey that idea best. Similarly, there are times where I start with a specific skeleton and fill it in, or other times I will start with more of an open palette and experiment until I find something that seems strong enough to inspire the rest of the compositional elements to fall into place around it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/260121225?color=ffffff&amp;amp;title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More broadly speaking, whether I’m composing music and sound design, making creative decisions regarding the broader scope of projects, selling through concepts and ideas, or even helping to steer our company’s entrepreneurial vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I try to do simultaneously define some kind of North Star or guiding principle, that I can always go back and ask “are we getting closer to the goal, are we on track?” but at the same time, to encourage and welcome dissent, to stay curious and open-minded, and realize we often come across better solutions and better questions then we had in mind when we started the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With all that said, I try to be pragmatic, and diligent at stepping forward rather than backward or sideways to actually get things done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/220858720?color=ffffff&amp;amp;title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;when-was-the-last-time-you-were-afraid-of-making-a-work-related-decision&quot;&gt;When was the last time you were afraid of making a work-related decision?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m often afraid of work-related decisions. These can range from simple production questions like, “should I put a guitar in this track?”, to broader business decisions like personnel, visions for the future of the studio, and what kind of projects we should work on. But these are fears with a lowercase ‘f’, and I think fear is an important driving factor in my creative work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As artists, we often are consumed by self-doubt and question our choices. I think overcoming these fears, embracing them or just putting your head down and pushing through them, is what makes us better artists and stronger human beings, and gives our life and our work meaning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I only worked on projects that were straightforward and didn’t require the need to doubt decisions, I’d likely just be making mindless and generic work, and I don’t think that would be a substantive professional existence. So, while excessive fear can be crippling, or at least counterproductive, personally I think it’s important to embrace and push through, rather than brushing it under the rug or avoiding it entirely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/285113069?color=ffffff&amp;amp;title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-do-you-stay-curious&quot;&gt;How do you stay curious?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s a great question and a very important concept to me. Especially as we grow up, get consumed by work, routine, families, and the mundane aspects of modern life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I try to seek out new music, art and experience, that open my mind to different emotions, ideas, thought processes, and techniques. First, I try to keep an open mind and try new things, especially things that scare you or take you out of your comfort zone. Second, maintaining an interesting and diverse group of peers, that bring different perspectives and taste to help broaden my awareness of Art, culture and more. Finally, more specific to my work composing music and crafting sound, I find that using particular tools and techniques, or setting limits on how to structure the creative process, helps keep me curious by diving into new areas that I might overlook or remain ignorant of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/9499310?color=ffffff&amp;amp;title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have the great luxury of working in a studio where we have all kinds of tools and toys, and I think when you have a lot of things at your fingertips, you can revert to common tricks and techniques that you’ve used before.  While this is one of the luxuries of having all kinds of fun gear and instruments, it’s also important to place limitations on yourself sometime so you can actually dive into a particular instrument or sound and find something new.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-are-you-most-excited-about-looking-at-the-year-ahead&quot;&gt;What are you most excited about looking at the year ahead?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, we had a great year in 2018, we worked hard on building solid systems, and a fantastic team, so that we could focus on what we do best - the work. We celebrated our 10-year anniversary with all three studios (New York, São Paulo and Amsterdam) for a week in Mexico. There, we spent a lot of time patting ourselves on the back for making it this far, but focusing on about what the next 1/3/5/10 years will look like for Antfood and what we can do to remain relevant as well as continue to get better over the coming decade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifically for 2019, we are developing a couple of new means of production, both for the AR/VR space, and for nonlinear games and experiences, but also for mixing custom, multi-channel audio in physical spaces. We’ve developed some neat tools for playing with sound and space, and I’m hoping we can convince some clients and collaborators to help us bring them to a larger audience!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/192041048?color=ffffff&amp;amp;title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m looking forward to our amazing team to continuing to grow and evolve and be able to take on more unique projects and challenges. We’re building a new (and hopefully) fresh platform based on machine learning to help organize and repurpose our back catalog of work. Finally, I hope we have the chance to continue working with our favorite people and meet some new ones to craft amazing audio work that moves people and gives some meaning to those who helped create it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See more of Antfood’s work at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.antfood.com/&quot;&gt;antfood.com&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/antfood.music/&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/antfood&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/antfood&quot;&gt;Vimeo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.google.com/blog/antfood-are-amazing/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.google.com/blog/antfood-are-amazing/</guid>
        
        <category>inspiration</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer of Siteleaf</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Summer is the time for sun, sea, and Siteleaf. No, really.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lots of festivals use Siteleaf to manage their sites. Siteleaf makes it easy for content creators to update static sites while still optimizing for site speed. Here are a few of our favorites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Outside-lands-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Image of two women wearing backpacks climbing stairs at a festival&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;outside-lands&quot;&gt;Outside Lands&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With sets from Janet Jackson, The Weekend, DJ Snake, Chvrches, Janelle Monáe, Carley Rae Jepson, and fifty more artists you can be sure that there’s something for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sfoutsidelands.com/&quot;&gt;Outside Lands&lt;/a&gt; is a festival that takes it’s food as seriously as it’s beats. Featuring goodies from the top talent in the Bay Area including truffled grilled cheeses, arepas, Taiwanese snow cones, and liquid chocolate bars. We’re not even sure what a liquid chocolate bar is, but you can bet we want to try one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They still have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sfoutsidelands.com/passes/&quot;&gt;tickets&lt;/a&gt; available for the weekend, including VIP passes if you’re feeling fancy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Grandoozy-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Image of white male singer holding a mic and addressing crowd&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;grandoozy&quot;&gt;Grandoozy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.grandoozy.com/&quot;&gt;Grandoozy&lt;/a&gt; has a sweet line up including Kendrick Lemar, Florence and the Machine, as well as the legendary Stevie Wonder. You can also break it down in the all-day dance area, which takes inspiration from Berlin’s infamous club scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Showcasing Denver’s craft brewery scene Grandoozy features 18 different breweries alongside Denver’s top distillers. Get involved and snap up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.grandoozy.com/tickets/&quot;&gt;tickets&lt;/a&gt; for this September’s festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Clusterfest-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Image of African American woman holding mic doing stand up comedy&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;clusterfest&quot;&gt;Clusterfest&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.clusterfest.com/&quot;&gt;Clusterfest&lt;/a&gt; is a comedy festival in San Fransisco, featuring comedians like Amy Schumer, Trevor Noah, and Tiffany Haddish alongside drag royalty Bianca Del Rio and Jinkx Monsoon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could also step into some of your favorite comedy shows with Clusterfest’s unique experiences. Slip into Paddy’s Pub (from it’s Always Sunny in Philadelphia) for a pint, or munching down a Bluth’s Frozen Banana (from Arrested Development). Sadly Clusterfest is all out of bananas for 2018, but there’s always next June!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Bristol-Comedy-garden-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Image of people in a park chatting and sipping beer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bristol-comedy-garden&quot;&gt;Bristol Comedy Garden&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the pond in England is a comedy festival that’s taking the South West by storm. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bristolcomedygarden.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Bristol Comedy Garden&lt;/a&gt; allows you to catch the best British comedians like Josh Widdicombe, Shappi Korsandi, and Alan Davis in a relaxed environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bristol Comedy Garden is a bargain, with tickets for each evening ranging from £20-£25. So it’s no surprise that they sold out every show this year. Keep your eyes on their colorful &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bristolcomedygarden.co.uk/&quot;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt; to see when next year’s line up gets announced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Grandoozy-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Image of young women at the front of a festival stage excited&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you use Siteleaf for a festival, event, or conference? Let us know on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/siteleaf&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 13:07:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.google.com/blog/summer-of-siteleaf/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.google.com/blog/summer-of-siteleaf/</guid>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>inspiration</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New sites in Siteleaf's gallery</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re probably a little biased, but we think the best sites use Siteleaf. Some of our favorites include &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wadejeffree.com/&quot;&gt;Wade Jeffree&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://girlsnightinclub.com/&quot;&gt;Girls’ Night In&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://upperquad.com/&quot;&gt;Upperquad&lt;/a&gt;. This week we added nine new sites to our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/gallery/&quot;&gt;gallery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;capitol-cider-house&quot;&gt;Capitol Cider House&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Capitol-cider-house.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Capitol Cider House website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://capitolciderhouse.com/&quot;&gt;Capitol Cider House&lt;/a&gt; is a new bar in Washington DC dedicated to showcasing cider producers within 200 miles of the Capitol building. They’ve even got a dog-friendly outside area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;canlis&quot;&gt;Canlis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Canlis-image.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Canlis website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just looking at the James Beard award-winning restaurant &lt;a href=&quot;https://canlis.com/&quot;&gt;Canlis&lt;/a&gt;’ website makes us hungry. And sad that we don’t live in Seattle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dine&quot;&gt;Dine&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/dine-image.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Dine website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dinehq.com/&quot;&gt;Dine&lt;/a&gt; is a creative design studio based in Beijing, who focus on designing for startups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dipmat&quot;&gt;Dipmat&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/dipmat-image.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Dipmat website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dimpat.com.au/&quot;&gt;Dipmat&lt;/a&gt; is an Architectural Building company based in Melbourne set up by friends Adrian Poropat and Bevan Dimeck. The buildings they bring to life are #goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;earn-studios&quot;&gt;Earn Studios&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/earn-image.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Earn Studios website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.earnstudios.com/&quot;&gt;Earn Studios&lt;/a&gt; are a team of strategists and inventors based in London who work with clients including Samsung, Univeral, and EE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;light-and-shade-media&quot;&gt;Light and Shade Media&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/light-shade-image.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Light and Shade Media website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://lightandshademedia.com/&quot;&gt;Light and Shade Media&lt;/a&gt; are an Australian production house specializing in commercial production, documentaries, and online advertising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;single-double&quot;&gt;Single Double&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/single-double-image.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Single Double website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://singledouble.co/&quot;&gt;Single Double&lt;/a&gt; is an independent content agency in Melbourne. They are passionate about turning brands into publishers and making content people love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;south-california-craft-coffee&quot;&gt;South California Craft Coffee&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/south-cali-image.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of South California Craft Coffee website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Built by coffee and Siteleaf aficionado John Choura Jr., &lt;a href=&quot;http://socal.coffee/&quot;&gt;South California Craft Coffee&lt;/a&gt; is a curated list of great spots for your next caffeine fix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;welcome-conference&quot;&gt;Welcome Conference&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/welcome-image.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of Welcome Conference website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://thewelcomeconference.com/&quot;&gt;Welcome Conference&lt;/a&gt; is a place for hospitality professionals to come together in New York City. Their June conference line up includes Seth Meyers, Victoria Arlen, and Alan Mulally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;See all the other sites #builtwithsiteleaf on our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/gallery/&quot;&gt;gallery&lt;/a&gt;. 
Want to see your website in our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/gallery/&quot;&gt;gallery&lt;/a&gt;? Get in touch on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/siteleaf&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:support@siteleaf.com&quot;&gt;email us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 13:08:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.google.com/blog/new-sites-in-siteleafs-gallery/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.google.com/blog/new-sites-in-siteleafs-gallery/</guid>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>inspiration</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Publishing a new blog post</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/264631007?title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;Watch &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/264631007&quot;&gt;Publishing a new blog post&lt;/a&gt; on Vimeo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, we’ll go through how to write and publish a new blog post. To get caught up on Familiarizing yourself with Siteleaf watch our previous video in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/blog/siteleaf-for-content-managers-and-creators/&quot;&gt;Siteleaf for Content Managers and Creators&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;writing-a-new-blog-post&quot;&gt;Writing a new blog post&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Head up to the sidebar and click on Posts, located in the content section of the sidebar. When you click on posts, you’ll see something like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/1-screen-shot-of-posts-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;1-screen-shot-of-posts-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To create a new post press the plus icon on the right side and it’ll take you to a screen that looks like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/2-screen-shot-blank-post-small-6555ef.png&quot; alt=&quot;2-screen-shot-blank-post-small-6555ef.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start by typing your title up at the top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to specify your URL, you can do that underneath the title, but if you leave it blank Siteleaf will do all the hard work for you and the slug (that’s the end of the URL) will be the title of the blogpost separated by hyphens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having slugs that are readable by both humans and machines is good for SEO because it encourages users to click on the link as they already understand the content of the post. It also tells the web crawlers hanging out online what the main subject of the post is about, which will help generate traffic to your site. Read more about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/blog/seo-with-jekyll-siteleaf/&quot;&gt;SEO with Jekyll and Siteleaf here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Underneath the URL in the big box is where you write the content for your post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;visual-mode&quot;&gt;Visual Mode&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the moment we will start in visual mode, and I’ll go into detail later on about &lt;a href=&quot;#markdown&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt;. Visual mode is currently in beta so sometimes it isn’t perfect, but it’s pretty smart and gets there 90% of the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/3-screen-shot-visual-mode-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;3-screen-shot-visual-mode-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are used to seeing changes immediately in Microsoft Word and other similar programs this will be helpful for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;formatting&quot;&gt;Formatting&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The default setting for the text is paragraph, but you can use the toolbar at the top to style the text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;headings&quot;&gt;Headings&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a hierarchy of headings built in by your website’s designer. You may want to check with them for usage guidance. But in general, Heading 1 will be the biggest and most eye-catching, Heading 2 will be a bit smaller, a bit less eye-catching and Heading 3 will be smaller still and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To insert a heading, highlight the text that you want to become a heading, then choose from the drop down which type of heading you would like to apply to the text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/4-screen-shot-heading-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;4-screen-shot-heading-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Bold&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can add bold styling do this by highlighting and pressing the bold icon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/5-screen-shot-bold-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;5-screen-shot-bold-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;italics&quot;&gt;Italics&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use italics highlight the text that you want to make italic, then choose the italic from the drop-down menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/6-screen-shot-italic-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;6-screen-shot-italic-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;quotes&quot;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can style a quote by highlighting the quotation and then pressing the quote icon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/7-screen-shot-quote-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;7-screen-shot-quote-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;code-snippet&quot;&gt;Code snippet&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you wanted to share a code snippet; style it by highlighting the text and then choose the code option from the drop-down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/8-screen-shot-code-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;8-screen-shot-code-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Code snippets can be helpful for technical blogs, and we use it a lot on our blog.  But if you’re writing about gardening, you can ignore this option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;lists&quot;&gt;Lists&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can make a bullet point (or “unordered”) list by clicking on the bullet list icon, and a numbered (or “ordered”) list by clicking on the numbered list icon next to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/9-screen-shot-list-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;9-screen-shot-list-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;adding-hyperlinks&quot;&gt;Adding Hyperlinks&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can add hyperlinks by highlighting the text that you want to become a link then clicking the link button in the toolbar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then you’ll see this input where you can add the URL to the website you’d like to direct people to. Once you have pasted that URL in and pressed ‘ok’ the hyperlink will be created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/10-screen-shot-hyperlink-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;10-screen-shot-hyperlink-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;adding-images&quot;&gt;Adding Images&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, you will want to add some images to this post, so it’s not a big wall of text. First tap the image icon and this pop-up will appear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/11-screen-shot-image-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;11-screen-shot-image-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can drag and drop your images to upload or choose the files from your computer. Also, you can click over to the ‘existing uploads’ tab to discover all the images previously uploaded to Siteleaf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing you will want to do is place your cursor where you’d like the image to be in your post. Then click on the image button again, and the pop-up will reappear. Then click over to the ‘existing uploads’ tab and select the image you want to input by pressing insert underneath the image. Then you will see the image in the text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;adding-emojis&quot;&gt;Adding Emojis&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siteleaf will accept emojis in the same way that any other input field would. If you’re on Windows, you can choose the desired emoji from your touch keyboard. Or you can bring up an emoji keyboard on your mac by pressing &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;command&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;control&lt;/code&gt; and the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;space bar&lt;/code&gt; at the same time and clicking on the desired emoji 🚀&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;markdown&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you change the view to Markdown from the drop-down in the toolbar, you’ll see that instead of generating a preview of the text styling we saw before there’s a lot of symbols.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/12-screen-shot-markdown-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;12-screen-shot-markdown-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Markdown was created as a simple way for non-programmers to write in an easy-to-read format that could be converted directly into HTML. It uses very simple formatting to accomplish the same thing that HTML or Rich Text Formatting does, but thankfully it’s simpler than HTML because you don’t have to worry about opening and closing tags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One benefit of Markdown is that the formatting is embedded in the text, so when you copy the text from different programs the styling comes too. There’s nothing more frustrating than formatting something perfectly in a program like Word or Pages, just to lose all the formatting that you’ve added when you copy and paste the text elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another advantage for me is that Markdown uses punctuation and characters that I already know and use. Which means I’m not hunting around on the keyboard to try to remember where an umlaut is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are lots of programs out there which help you write in Markdown as it’s such a versatile way of writing, you should check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bear-writer.com/&quot;&gt;Bear&lt;/a&gt; because it’s bear-y good or &lt;a href=&quot;https://ia.net&quot;&gt;iA Writer&lt;/a&gt; which also works on Android as well as iOS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;formatting-1&quot;&gt;Formatting&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;headings-1&quot;&gt;Headings&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With markdown headings are done with the hash key, or as some of you might know it the pound key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;# HEADLINE&lt;/code&gt; is a large header. &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;## HEADLINE&lt;/code&gt; would be a header that was a little smaller than the first, and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;### HEADLINE&lt;/code&gt; would be a smaller header still.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;italics-1&quot;&gt;Italics&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For italics, you want to put an asterisk or star either side of the word or phrase that you want to become &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;*italic*&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;bold-1&quot;&gt;Bold&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make text bold put two asterisks or stars either side of the word or phrase you want to &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;**bold**&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;quote&quot;&gt;Quote&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To turn your quotation into quote formatting put a &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; greater than symbol at the start of the new line with the quote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;code-snippet-1&quot;&gt;Code snippet&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add a code snippet simply add a ` backtick either side of the text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;lists-1&quot;&gt;Lists&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to make a numbered list (also known as an ordered list) simply start a new line and type &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;1.&lt;/code&gt; and then on the next line type &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;2.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d prefer to make a bullet point list (also known as an unordered list) just pop a dash on a new line each time you want a new bullet point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;adding-hyperlinks-1&quot;&gt;Adding Hyperlinks&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add a link surround the word or phase in square brackets and then paste the link in parenthesis after, and boom you have a link.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;[text](www.intendedhyperlink.com)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can still use the link button in the toolbar for any of these functions if it’s easier for you, it isn’t one or the other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;adding-images-1&quot;&gt;Adding Images&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inserting an image purely in Markdown is a little more tricky. Typically if I’m writing a draft somewhere outside of Siteleaf, I’ll put something like ‘INSERT IMAGE HERE’ in the text and then input the image the same way as described earlier on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it is achievable in Markdown and inserting an image works in the same way as adding a hyperlink. But you have to know the title that the image had when you uploaded it to Siteleaf. To insert an image in Markdown on a new line put:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;![](link to where the image lives on Siteleaf)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The location of the image will be along the lines of &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/uploads/filename&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Between the square brackets, you need to add the image’s alt tag. Alt tags are used by screen readers, the browsers used by blind and visually impaired people, to tell them what the image shows. Also, bots use alt tags to understand the image, and this helps your SEO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s more on our blog about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/blog/seo-with-jekyll-siteleaf/&quot;&gt;SEO with Jekyll and Siteleaf&lt;/a&gt;, which you should read for further SEO tips and best practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;before-you-publish&quot;&gt;Before you publish&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a few last steps you’ll want to do before making your post visible, and these will vary depending on how your site is set up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/21-screen-shot-metadata-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;21-screen-shot-metadata-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may find metadata fields beneath the main text input. On our site, there’s a field where you can upload an image that will be displayed when you share the link online, which makes people more inclined to click on the link. Also, there is a field where you can post a description of the blog post. These act like a preview in the same way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are called ‘rich previews’ and are particularly useful when posting links on social media like Facebook or in Slack channels as it gives your readers a flavor of what they will see before they click on the link, making them more inclined to click on and read further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d advise speaking to your Admin or Developer about the metadata fields on your site and the best way to use them. You can find more &lt;a href=&quot;https://learn.siteleaf.com/content/metadata/&quot;&gt;technical information on metadata here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;flight-panel&quot;&gt;Flight Panel&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the right on the main text input, you can see the flight panel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/22-screen-shot-flight-panel-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;22-screen-shot-flight-panel-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;save&quot;&gt;Save&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This button is where you save your changes. Should you forget to save the changes you’ve made and click away from what you’re editing, Siteleaf will prompt you with a pop up to check if you want to leave these unsaved changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Underneath there are three options for your post, either ‘Draft’, ‘Hidden’ or ‘Visible’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;draft&quot;&gt;Draft&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Draft status is for posts that you are currently working on and shouldn’t yet be made public - or if your role is Writer, then this is how all of your posts will be saved before an Admin or Publisher makes them Visible. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/blog/siteleaf-for-content-managers-and-creators/#roles&quot;&gt;Learn more about roles on Siteleaf&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;hidden&quot;&gt;Hidden&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hidden posts are exactly that - hidden. These can be useful if you’ve written about your undying love for Chicago style pizza only to discover that you prefer New York style pizza and can’t have your previous opinion all over the internet. As a side note, all pizza is great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;visible&quot;&gt;Visible&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the posts that you’ve written that you want the whole world to read should be set to visible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;tags&quot;&gt;Tags&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We like to use tags on our blog posts so that users can go through the tags to connect with other posts you tagged with the same tag in the past. For example, under the tag ‘pizza’ your readers can click through to see all your past pizza blog posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is great for UX because then someone can press on the tag, like ‘announcements’ or ‘pizza’, and see all the pizza posts on your site. This is also great for SEO. The more thoroughly you use tags, the easier it is for your readers and web crawlers to engage with your content across years of blog posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;categories&quot;&gt;Categories&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are very similar to tags, but with broader groupings. Tags and categories are similar, and their purpose is to sort your content to improve the usability of your site. Meaning when a user comes to your site, they can easily browse through your content by category or by tag rather than browsing chronologically, which is how blogs were initially set up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/24-screen-shot-categories-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;24-screen-shot-categories-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These work in much the same way as tags, and you can use them together. For example, you can use the category ‘recipe’ whenever you talk about something you tried to cook, but you can use much more specific tags like ‘pizza’, ‘tacos’, or ‘salad’ too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should talk with your developer or site admin to see what is best for your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;date&quot;&gt;Date&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the date which the post was published. If you set it to a date in the future, it won’t automatically publish on that date unless you set up a scheduled or automatic publishing schedule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/25-screen-shot-date-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;25-screen-shot-date-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recommend using Zapier for this task. With Zapier, and you can use it to integrate your Siteleaf site with lots of different applications like Trello, Twitter, Typeform and other apps not beginning with the letter T. &lt;a href=&quot;https://zapier.com/apps/schedule/integrations/siteleaf/15388/publish-siteleaf-every-day-at-a-scheduled-time&quot;&gt;Head to Zapier for more information&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;publishing-your-post&quot;&gt;Publishing your post&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Publish this post by changing the post’s status to ‘visible’ and hit save.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned in our last &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/blog/siteleaf-for-content-managers-and-creators/&quot;&gt;tutorial&lt;/a&gt;, I like to generate item preview before I publish a page, just to check that everything looks as I expected and that I haven’t accidentally added the wrong image or misspelled anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/26-screen-shot-preview-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;26-screen-shot-preview-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siteleaf generates a preview in this new tab. Once it’s ready you can check it over. If you’re happy with how it looks head back to Siteleaf’s tab to publish the post. Once you are confident everything looks great you can press ‘publish changes’ in the top right corner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/27-screen-shot-publishing-small.png&quot; alt=&quot;27-screen-shot-publishing-small.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will see that a loading animation takes over the blue bar at the top of Siteleaf. Once it’s published you can see the changes that you’ve made on your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes a new post might take a few minutes to show up because your website uses a cache. If this is the case you can access the direct URL and go ahead with sharing the post online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;stay-tuned&quot;&gt;Stay Tuned&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our next video will explain step by step how to embed videos in Siteleaf - stay tuned to the blog for that soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there’s anything you would like for us to cover in our tutorials please get in touch on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/siteleaf&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.google.com/blog/publishing-a-new-blog-post/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.google.com/blog/publishing-a-new-blog-post/</guid>
        
        <category>video</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Siteleaf for Content Managers and Creators</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/258881059?title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;Watch &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/258881059&quot;&gt;Siteleaf for Content Managers and Creators&lt;/a&gt; on Vimeo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our new series of tutorials will walk you through everything you need to know about adding content to your Siteleaf site. There’s no code involved, so you can feel confident using Siteleaf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;familiarizing-yourself-with-siteleaf&quot;&gt;Familiarizing yourself with Siteleaf&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you log in to your account you’ll see something like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20Dashboard.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot Dashboard.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the Siteleaf Dashboard. The first thing you’ll notice is the sidebar. Here are the elements of your website broken down into four sections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;content&quot;&gt;Content&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section is organized by collections — think of these as your main content buckets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This site has several collections, but you may only have a few options on yours. It depends on how your site has been set up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When looking at a new website I always click on each collection to familiarise myself with the content and then look at the published website to see how they relate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;pages&quot;&gt;Pages&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A page is the most basic content type in Siteleaf - these might include your ‘about’ page, or a ‘contact’ page. See more about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/siteleaf-for-content-managers-and-creators/#Editing-existing-pages&quot;&gt;how to edit existing pages here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;posts&quot;&gt;Posts&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a content creator, you’re most likely to want to know about the blog. Posts are connected to the blog page on your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20Posts.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot Posts.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your site does not have a blog, then feel free to ignore this section. You can click on the title of the post to edit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20SEO%20Blog%20Post.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot SEO Blog Post.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you click through to the post you’ll see up at the top is the title, you can click on it to edit it. Underneath is the post’s URL, and you can change the slug by clicking on the pencil icon. A slug is the editable part of your post’s URL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the URL of the post:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;https://www.siteleaf.com/blog/seo-with-jekyll-siteleaf/&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This part is the slug:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/seo-with-jekyll-siteleaf/&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having slugs that are readable by both humans and machines is useful for SEO. Readable slugs encourage users to click on the link, because they already understand what the post is about. Also, you are signposting your post to the web crawlers. For more tips on SEO read our blog post about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/blog/seo-with-jekyll-siteleaf/&quot;&gt;SEO with Jekyll and Siteleaf&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Underneath is all the main body content of the page. You may also see inputs for metadata beneath the main body content, these will vary depending on how your site is set up. We’ll go through metadata, tags, post visibility and more in our dedicated blog post video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;files&quot;&gt;Files&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;uploads&quot;&gt;Uploads&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is where your uploaded images, videos and documents live. Click here to browse or search for items uploaded to Siteleaf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20Uploads.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot Uploads.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siteleaf supports all document types; from jpegs to pdfs and mp4s. You can also add new items here by clicking ‘Upload file’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;site&quot;&gt;Site&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where all the data for your site’s source files live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20Site.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot Site.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a content creator, you aren’t going to want to touch it. And, depending on your user role, you may not see it on your Siteleaf dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;users&quot;&gt;Users&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here you can see who else has access to your website and what ‘role’ they have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20Users.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot Users.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re on a Team, Business, or Enterprise site plan, there are three different roles that users can be assigned. You can also add new users here by inputting their email address, assigning their role before pressing invite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;roles&quot;&gt;Roles&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;admin&quot;&gt;Admin&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This role has full privileges which means that you can manage and publish all content. This role is great for people who are helping build the site, like a developer or designer. Admin allows users to upload theme files, change the site’s settings, and invite other collaborators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;publisher&quot;&gt;Publisher&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is similar to the admin role but publishers can’t access theme files or the site’s settings. Publishers can manage and publish pages, posts, and uploads, but you’re protected from accidentally breaking the site’s theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;writer&quot;&gt;Writer&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the most limited role on Siteleaf. A Writer can only manage their own content, and any content that a Writer creates will default to ‘draft’ status. This means that a Publisher or Admin must approve a writer’s content first before publishing it. This role is great for sites with many collaborators who only need access to add content, like a blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel you haven’t got the right role for what you need to achieve on Siteleaf ask someone with the Admin role to change your settings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;settings&quot;&gt;Settings&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the details of your site’s settings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20Settings.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot Settings.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here you can edit settings or fields your developer may have created, like social media links or SEO descriptions. The options here will depend on your individual site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;editing-existing-pages&quot;&gt;Editing existing pages&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a great place to start getting your hands dirty. First click on Pages underneath Content and you will see something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20Pages.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot Pages.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are your website’s individual pages. You can click into each page by pressing on the title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, you can reorder the pages by dragging and dropping with the arrows. You can nest a page by sliding the item to the right until you see the outline indent underneath the page you want to become the parent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you go into one of the pages you will see something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20Purpose%20Page.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot Purpose Page.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the top is the page’s title, then following that is the URL of this particular page. You can edit this if you need by pressing on the pencil icon, like with the post earlier on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below is the main body text. This is where you’d write all your content for the page. Siteleaf supports Markdown formatting. We will go into Markdown in detail in our dedicated blog post tutorial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, below there may be different fields that your developer has created. These will be individual to your site and could include links to source material, header images or even background colors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;page-settings&quot;&gt;Page Settings&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pages only have two visibility options, they are either hidden or visible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20Flight%20Panel.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot Flight Panel.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hiding a page can be used while you are working on it. Or if you have a page that promotes your winter season you can hide that in the sweltering summer heat. If you are a Writer you will need to ask either an Admin or Publisher to make these changes for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click save to save the changes that you’ve made. I personally like to check the edits before I publish. You can do that by pressing generate item preview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20Preview.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot Preview.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will open up a new tab. Then you’ll see that Siteleaf is taking the changes that you’ve made and then updating the page. Once it’s generated the preview it’ll show you a message which you can click on to refresh the page with your edits. When I’m happy with these changes we can go back to Siteleaf to publish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;publishing-the-page&quot;&gt;Publishing the page&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can publish the changes by pressing the ‘Publish changes’ button in the top right-hand corner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/uploads/Screen%20Shot%20Publish%20changes-9d8357.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screen Shot Publish changes-9d8357.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a Writer on your site this button will not be visible. In this case, let a Publisher or Admin know when you’re ready to have your draft approved and then published.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Publishing should be pretty quick, but sometimes it takes a bit longer with a bigger website. Once it’s published you can see the changes that you’ve made on your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;stay-tuned&quot;&gt;Stay Tuned&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our next video will explain step by step how to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siteleaf.com/blog/publishing-a-new-blog-post/&quot;&gt;publish a new blog post in Siteleaf&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there’s anything you would like for us to cover in our tutorials please get in touch on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/siteleaf&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 10:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.google.com/blog/siteleaf-for-content-managers-and-creators/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.google.com/blog/siteleaf-for-content-managers-and-creators/</guid>
        
        <category>video</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
